ngolos.com 2017-12-07

# nGolos.com | Latest Video Highlights and Goals

Our website is made possible by displaying online advertisements to our visitors.  
Please consider supporting us by disabling your ad blocker.

###### **Privacy Policy**

* * *

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which nGolos.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.nGolos.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by nGolos.com.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising powered by Google to serve ads when you visit our website. Google may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Google, click [here.](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

Our primary advertising is provided by Google Adsense who utilize the doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads.

▹ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
▹ Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
▹ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

nGolos.com primarily utilizes the Google Analytics web service to monitor usage patterns and statistics of this website. As a result when you browse this website, some identifiable information will be shared with Google in order to aggregate statistics. We encourage you to read the Google privacy policy to familiarize yourself with how Google can use this information.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

nGolos.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

(Last Update: 2016/07/10)
